welcome to high business news this is
kanksha gangapuram and you are watching
National PR news Mangal industry is the
second largest subsidiary of amaraja
group of companies has witnessed
tremendous growth of over 450 crores in
FY 2021 and 22. with Revenue clocking
over 1400 crores having evolved as a
design LED Manufacturing Company Mangal
industry serves a board spectrum of
Industries with deep domain expertise in
Auto components metal fabrication
battery components tool Works Storage
Solutions and Customs fabrication
founded by the Visionary industrialist
and philanthropist Dr ramachandan and
Gala Mangal Industries was set up as a
small manufacturing unit to supply
components to the battery businesses it
has now grown up into a multi-product
company that lists some of the largest
brands in the country as its customers
currently the company employs over 3000
people and has become the second largest
within the USD 1.3 billion Raja group
Cosmo first limited a four decade old
Global business organization with
entities Cosmo films Cosmo Specialty
Chemicals announced the elevation of Mr
kulbush and Malik as the business had
further film business globally he was
earlierly working as the head of
operations for international businesses
a seasoned business leader with over 24
years of experience culbushan comes to
Cosmo films with diverse experience in
general management roles and with PL
responsibilities Business Development
and financial roles with a demonstrated
record of working in the manufacturing
industry Mr pankaj podar's group CEO
Cosmo first limited set kulbushan has
not only been an integral part of Cosmo
films growth but has helped navigate it
via his leadership strategy and business
acument I am confident that with cool
bhushan in charge Cosmo first will
continue to achieve its strategic
business goals
as always India's Global smart home
security company has expanded its
products line with the S Voice ty1 Wi-Fi
pan and tilt camera in India this 4 MP
camera provides a superior and
industry-leading indoor home security
experience that fits more families with
the 360 Degrees field of vision
h.265 video technology and smart
tracking functions that allows users to
monitor their property in two care
resolutions at all times while the Wi-Fi
segment is dominated by the 2mp cameras
is with a being Global leader has taken
the responsibilities of launch a much
needed product in 4 mp2 by 2K this 4 MP
camera includes a monitorized pan and
tilts for 360 Degree visual coverage
allowing users to watch the entire room
with one camera rather than needing
numerous cameras in various Corners
additionally it's 2K impressive
resolution is supported by Chris clear
footage that is sharpened with consumers
as an immediate alert by minimizing
areas of overexposure in the videos
displayed for sharper nighttime
surveillance of up to 10 meters the
is-west ty1 significantly enhances the
night vision
ICICI Lombard one of the leading private
General insurance companies launched a
slew of path breaking innovative
solutions within monitor Insurance aimed
at further enriching the end customers
experience the motor floater offer for
its consumers is in the line with the
recent announcement made by irdai it
will enable those individuals owning
multiple vehicles to ensure their
vehicles including cars and two wheelers
under one policy with a single renewal
date and a comprehensive cover as a
result now there can be a single motor
insurance policy for vehicles owned by
them this new offering makes it
convenient for consumers to have a
single policy repeat to have a single
policy and renewable date for all the
their motor policies along with a single
premium at the same time consumer
options for the motor floating's
offerings will be provided a lower
premium for the multiple vehicles
ensured under the motor floater offering
overall it will save consumers efforts
of maintaining multiple motor insurance
policies for each vehicle owned by them
Knight Frank in its recent edition of
Asia Pacific Prime office rental index
for Q2 2022 noted Delhi NCR as the 10th
most expensive commercial real estate
market in the APAC region the annual
Prime headline rent of commercial office
space in the cities was recorded by U.S
dollars 51.6 Square feets a year Hong
Kong SAR continues to be Asia's most
expensive office Market with an annual
rent of U.S dollars
175.4 square feet per year in terms of
annual growth Bengaluru witnessed the
higher Prime official rent percentage
increase of 12.1 percent yoy in Q2 2022
Mumbai achieved the highest quarterly
change at seven percent in its prime
office rentals value the ABAC office
rental index registered a growth of 1.0
percent quarter on quarter after gaining
of two consecutive quarters the overall
index is up to 2.0 percent yoy of the 23
cities tracking by the Knight Frank Asia
Pacific Prime office rental index 17
cities recorded stable or increased rent
in Q2 2022 as compared to 21 in the
previous quarter
Franklin templation India is launching
an open-ended Dynamic asset allocation
fund called Franklin India balance it
Advantage fund fibaf
the fund intended to generate long-term
capital appreciation and income
Generation by investing in a dynamically
managed portfolio of equity and Equity
related instruments and fixed income and
money market instruments fibaf offers
practical allocations between equity and
debt based on Market valuation and
fundamental factors driven views the
product is suitable for those who are
not only Keen to take advantage of the
growth opportunities in equities but
also prefer to reduce in the impact of
Market volatility the new fund offers
opens on August 16 2022 and August 30
2022 during which units will be
available for rupees 10 per unit
[Music]
after closing FY 22 with its best ever
Top Line since Inception India's largest
B2B e-commerce company and Junction
Services Limited kept growing curved and
hydrant in q1 of FY 23 the company's Top
Line in q1 grew 13 percent over the same
period last year and four percent over
the previous quarter value added grew 12
percent over the same period last year
and 14 percent over the last quarter of
fy22 chairman Mr MC Agarwal said not
resisting on our Laurels we are in the
process of identifying and finalizing
our new growth engines for FY 23 and
Beyond with the industry supporting and
the entire business ecosystem adopting
digitalization and transparency at a
phase Pace M Junction is at an
interesting juncture in its growth
trajectory MD Mr winnebama said while M
Junction continues to extend its
e-auction business to new categories it
expects a large number of Enterprises to
onboard its e-marketing place for
non-moving spares thank you for watching
signing off keep watching High business
news